Summary:

Stem cell and tissue engineering researcher at the Department of Biomedical Engineering at Texas A&M University with experience in sterile and non-sterile wet labs along with experimental design and project management. Consistent expertise in staining, cell culture, imaging, and data analysis. Competent in "**Technical Skills**".

Experience:

Stem Cell & Tissue Engineering Researcher | Department of BME & TAMU

August, 2023 - Present

Currently researching novel skin graft ECM scaffolds along with bioreactors and cardiac fibroblasts under the Zhao Lab. Currently leading 2 projects and am a major contributor to 3 others while mentoring an undergrad and high school student.

Skills: Solidworks, KLayout, Cell Cultures (hDF, hiPSC, hMSC, CF), DNA assay, IF staining, Zeiss AxOb5 scope, ZEN Pro, R figures/stats, Mentorship, Experimental Design

Grant Funded Research Intern | UPMC Children's Hospital of Pittsburgh

May - July, 2023

Performed Kidney/Bladder/UTI research in the department of pediatrics and the department of nephrology under Dr. Catherine Forster's mentorship through the SRIP (Student Research Internship Program) provided by UPMC Children's Hospital of Pittsburgh, University of Pittsburgh, and a PHS Grant.

Award: I was awarded a travel grant to ASN Kidney Week that totaled \$3000 as a result of my research.

Skills: Laboratory Safety, Laboratory Skills, IACUC Clearance, Immunohistochemistry, Microtomy, Hematoxylin & Eosin stains, Leica DMi8 scope, Small animal work (mouse).

Emergency Room Clinical Volunteer | CHI St. Joseph Health

January, 2023 - July, 2024

Turned over used rooms quickly, responded to patient needs (within my scope), and took vitals...

Skills: Patient Care, Vital Signs, Communication

Education:

Texas A&M University College of Engineering

August 2022 - Present

Biomedical Engineering student within the Craig and Galen Brown Engineering Honors program through the President's Endowed and National Merit Recognition Scholarships.

GPA: 3.4 (unweighted) - 112 Credit Hours (Fall 2022 - Summer 2024 semesters)

Languages

Native/Bilingual proficiency in English and Korean.

Technical Skills

Solidworks, KLayout, Labview, Python, Git, Vim, Java, R, Rust, Typescript, Javascript, HTML5, CSS, React, SQL, PostgreSQL, Supabase, CORS, CSP, Proxy server, Node.js, Heroku, Web scraping, Kotlin, Swift, C#, Lua, Pytorch (CUDA), MatLab, Batch scripting